BARBARA USSHER

SUMMARY

Hardworking receptionist with eight years of experience. Experience in customer service, issuing invoices, making appointments, and providing clients with optimal information about the company.

Fluent in English and Spanish. Sociable, enthusiastic, proactive, and adept at multitasking to achieve individual and team goals, looking forward to joining a new team

SKILLS

- Team player
- Oral and written communications
- Responsibility
- Excellent interpersonal communications
- Attention to detail
- Proactive

- Microsoft Office
- Organization
- Customer service
- Management of social networks
- Sociable
- Multitasking

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Front Desk Receptionist Berlitz

12/2020 to Present Dublin, Ireland

- Greet visitors and students
- Provide information and answer queries from walk-ins
- Deal with telephone enquiries.
- Assist with reception duties
- Coordinate weekly and monthly admin report (Bookings and Enquiries)
- Assist with financial & accounting activities
- Manage administration duties as required
- Ensure student details are logged accurately on CLASS

03/2014 to 06/2019

Receptionist / Administrative Baf S.R.L

Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Front desk responsibilities and administrative duties.
- Greet clients and provide them with information about the company.
- Managed telephone and email enquiries
- Ordering office supplies
- Coordinated and scheduled all company meetings, appointments, and interviews.
- In charge of payroll distribution.
- Issued invoices.

EDUCATION

Flight Attendant 2017

Escuela Aeronavegantes Buenos Aires, Argentina

Training education to become a flight attendant

High School Degree 2011

Institute Santísima Virgen Niña Buenos Aires, Argentina

Commercial expert with orientation in administration and management of corporations

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Volunteering 01/2015 to 01/2018

Pastoral Center "Dulce Nombre de María" Coordinator of activities, workshops, and games for children Buenos Aires, Argentina